# **Zubair Ahmad**

LARAVEL Web Developer

## **PROFILE**

Hey! I am Zubair, A LARAVEL Developer having more than 1 years of experience of working on Ecommerce Websites and various reporting dashboards. I started my freelance career back in 2021. Up till now, I have developed many projects. I help clients by developing a high-impact, Creative, & User Interactive Projects for them. Our highly expert experienced team members can help you create a profitable E-Commerce business websites based on your requirements. I work with clients all over the globe and have developed a professional bond of trust and honesty with them with my

## CONTACT



+92 316 0745530



Zubairahmad14451@gmail.com



Samanabad, Faisalabad

## **EDUCATION**

Govt Post Graduate College Faisalabad. 2017-2019

ICS

SOFTECH COMPUTER TRAINING, Faisalabad. 2020-21

Bachelor's Degree in Web Development.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Web Developer / ARN Solutions 2021-2022 LARAVEL Developer/Optimum Tech 2022-current

- LARAVEL PHP website design
- custom LARAVEL web development
- web customization
- Responsive websites | Design
- E-Commerce business websites.
- Design & develop online brand creative pieces including landing pages, banners and emails.
- Create comps for new and updated web pages for social and ecommerce partners.
- Payment method with card
- Delivery Status
- Email Verification
- Attach with whatsapp
- Comment replay system
- Auto bill send to mail/download file system

### HIGHLIGHTED SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS3
- Bootstrap
- J query
- PHP
- LARAVEL
- Ajax

# Languages

- English
- Urdu